原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
法庭開庭了
Court is fucking in session!
翻譯     阿鹿  RiverSide152  小酸奶
《末日逼近》前情提要
他就是通過恐懼控制你們嗎
Is that all he has over you? Is fear?
翻譯     冰島豆腐  蘇葵  哈里不是波特
洛伊德  開槍打死他
Lloyd, fucking shoot that man.
沒有你的恐懼  他一無是處
That he's nothing without your fear!
校對     RiverSide152
時間軸     樹  暴走小罐頭
感覺不對
It doesn't feel right.
這不對勁
Something's not right!
后期     漁夫
總監     RiverSide152
不
No!
血債血還  血債血還
Make them pay! Make them pay!
血債血還
Make them pay!
開始派對吧
Let's get this party started.
有遺言嗎
Any last words?
-我無懼惡魔  -閉嘴
- I will fear no evil! - Shut up!
我給你帶來了火
I brought you the fire.
他不在了
He's gone.
誰
Who is?
暗黑者
The Dark Man.
你能看到他嗎  你能看到斯圖嗎  小喬
Can you see him? Can you see... can you see Stu, Joe?
小喬  小喬  告訴我  你能看到斯圖嗎
Joe, tell me, can you see Stu? Can...
該死
Oh, shit.
希望我可以說  每個故事都有完美結局
I wish I could tell you every story has a happy ending.
但事實是  大部分故事根本不會結束
Truth is, most stories don't end at all.
不完全結束
Not really.
感覺我們每一天都在進步
Feels like every day we're making progress.
但問題是  我們將去向何方
But the question is where are we headed,
到達終點尚需多久
and how much farther do we have to go before we get there?
還要多久才能重建完畢  正常生活
How long before we go from rebuilding back to just living again?
這個地方還要多久
And how long after that before this place
才能回到以前的光景
goes back to being just like before?
有時感覺"崔普斯上尉"就像撥了個開關
Sometimes it feels like Captain Trips was like flipping a breaker switch.
一切皆新  人們有機會去改變一切
Everything's new, a chance to do it all different.
但是我每一天都在想  會嗎
But every day I wonder-- will we?
這一次  我們會作出改變嗎
Will we do anything different this time?
甚至  我們能作出改變嗎
Can we, even? Are we capable?
所以  你來到了我身邊
Which brings me to you.
來到這世上時  你是如此完美
When you got here, you were perfect.
6.7斤重  我從未想到自己一直渴望擁有你
Seven pounds, six ounces of everything I never knew I always wanted.
所有人都拿出了酒
Everyone broke out the liquor.
幾乎把所有囤著的酒都拿了出來
Just about all the booze we'd been hoarding,
為你的出生
raised in a toast to you,
為你所擁有的未來而舉杯歡慶
to the future you promised.
派對熱鬧非凡
It was a hell of a party.
然后
And then...
溫醫生和我互相鼓勁
Dr. Wen and I tried telling each other
可能只是義膜性喉炎而已
it was probably just croup or something.
或是普通流感  絕不會是"崔普斯上尉"
Even regular flu. Anything but that.
但之后  你的脖子開始腫脹
But then, your neck started to swell.
確定你患上了"崔普斯上尉"后
As soon as it was clear you had Trips,
我們不斷自問
we all asked ourselves the question.
73億人感染了"崔普斯上尉"
7.3 billion people caught Captain Trips.
73億人死亡
7.3 billion people died.
無人痊愈
Not one person recovered.
完全沒有希望
There was no hope.
我們怎么能眼看你承受痛苦
How could we let you suffer?
我憎恨自己曾有過那個念頭
I hate that the notion ever crossed my mind,
但我必須坦白
but it feels important to tell you that it did.
但沒有辦法  我做不到
But there was no way. I just couldn't.
我知道格倫會說  為了減輕自己的負罪感
I know Glen would say it was selfish
而放任你受苦是非常自私的行為
let you keep suffering to spare my conscience.
也許他是對的吧  我不知道
Maybe he'd be right. I don't know.
沒有人聽說過  得了"崔普斯上尉"的人會有所好轉
No one had ever heard of someone improving once they caught Trips.
我們眼見耳聞的患者在死前
Everyone we'd seen or heard about just got worse
情況只會越來越糟糕
and worse until they died.
即使我知道你康復了
Even when I knew we had you back,
那畫面也揮之不去
I couldn't shake the image.
在眾多空的嬰兒床之間  你就躺在那里
There you were, surrounded by all those empty cribs.
當然這些嬰兒床不會一直空著
Of course, they won't stay empty.
珍和泰勒·柯蒂斯的孩子比你出生晚十周
Jen and Tyler Curtis' baby was just ten weeks behind you.
早產兒
He came early.
但他沒有得"崔普斯上尉"
But he never got Trips.
免疫父母誕下的第一位孩子  目前一切順利
First baby born to two immune parents. So far, so good.
也許  還有希望
Maybe there's hope for us yet.
天啊  真希望你能見見斯圖
God, I wish you could meet Stu.
大家一直讓我派人去維加斯
People keep trying to get me to send scouts to Vegas,
看看能否發現我們的人究竟發生了什么事
see if they can find out what happened to our people,
弗拉格究竟怎么樣了  為什么天上會出現那種光線
to Flagg, what made those lights in the sky.
我一直說  不  太危險了  我們沒有多余的人力了
I keep saying, "No, it's too dangerous, we can't spare the manpower."
可能我只是不想知道答案吧
Is it possible I just don't want to know the answer?
我還要多久才能接受他已經死去的事實
I mean, how long do I wait before I accept that he must be dead?
還要多久我才不會再夢見他
And how long until I stop dreaming about him?
快看  你好呀
Hey, look at... H-hi!
剛好  我討厭一個人抬嬰兒車下樓梯
Perfect timing. I hate going down these stairs alone.
你們繼續走  我等會再趕上你們
You guys carry on, okay? I'll-I'll catch up.
我們正要去為今晚布置場地
We're, uh, just on our way to help set up for tonight.
對
Oh, yeah.
我現在還不想被人群包圍
Yeah, I don't f... I don't feel much like being around people right now.
嗯
Yeah.
希望你有打算過來
Well, I-I hope you're planning on coming down.
人們見到你很重要
You know, it's important that people see you,
見到你們倆
you out there and, you know, both of you.
好
Yeah.
你是我們剩下的人和她之間唯一的聯系
You're the only connection that the rest of us still have to her.
直到其他人回來
Until the others get back.
嗯
Right.
直到他們回來
Till they come back.
我
Hey, I...
你是真的嗎
Are you real?
過一會兒再來問我
Ask me again in a little while.
湯姆救了我的命  弗蘭妮
Tom saved my life, Frannie.
見見艾比蓋爾
Meet Abagail.
艾比蓋爾
Abagail.
艾比  這是你爸爸
Hey, Abby. Meet your daddy.
你好呀  小姑娘
Hey, there, girl.
艾比蓋爾
Hey, Abagail.
末日逼近  第一季  第九集[本季終]
科羅拉多州博爾德市
加入我們的國慶節燒烤會
讓小朋友到我這里來
大家慢點
Let's slow it down, people.
我喜歡這首歌
I love this song.
我馬上回來
I'll be back.
出什么事了嗎  親愛的
Something wrong, honey?
沒有
No.
沒有  我也不知道
Nothing. I don't know.
你肯定知道
I'll bet you do.
你多半會以為我瘋了
I think you'll think I'm crazy.
這可說不定  要不你說說看
Aw. Don't know about that. Why don't you try me?
我想回緬因  去看大海
I want to go back to Maine, see the ocean.
博爾德很不錯  很安全
I mean, Boulder's wonderful, a-and it's safe...
不
Well, no.
比外面安全  我知道
Safer than out there. I know that.
這里有文明和我們的朋友  但是
I mean, there's civilization and our friends are here, but it just...
感覺很...
feels like it's so...
我不...在這一切之中
I don't... in the middle of things.
二月的時候  我知道所有人的名字
You know, back in February, I knew everyone by their first name?
雪融了之后  我們又多了五百人
Then all the snow went, and we've got 500 more.
至少五百人
At least 500.
三個在監獄里
Three in jail.
現在只有酒鬼  騷亂和破壞公物
Only drunk and disorderly and vandalism right now,
但遲早會變得更糟
but sooner or later it's gonna be something worse.
-偷盜和...  -謀殺
- Stealing and... - Murder.
我不想這么想  不過是的
I mean, I don't want to think that way, but yeah.
教母會稱其為老亞當[本性之惡]
Mother would have called it the Old Adam.
總是會顯露出來
It always comes out.
你說的跟我想的一樣嗎
Are you saying what I think you are?
你愿意讓孩子冒風險嗎
Will you risk the baby?
凡事都有風險
Everything's a risk.
即使是現在  沒有了弗拉格
Even now, with Flagg gone.
我們不用留下  我們可以回來
We don't have to stay. We could come back.
嗯  是可以
Yeah. We could do that.
回來然后...  看看大家過得怎么樣
Come back and just... if only to see how folks are making out.
你能考慮下嗎
Will you think about it?
我會考慮的
Yeah, I'll think about it.
與此同時  你能陪我跳這支舞嗎
In the meantime, may I have this dance?
你想什么時候走
So, when do you want to go?
你是真心的嗎
Do you really mean it?
我把那些東西都帶上了  不是嗎
Mm, brought all those, didn't I?
這里越來越吵了  是嗎
Yeah, it's getting a little loud here, isn't it?
這還不是紐約  但是
I mean, it ain't New York City yet, but...
你想什么時候出發
When do you want to take off?
-很快  -是嗎
- Soon. - Yeah?
越快越好
As soon as we possible.
回到原點
Close the circle.
沒錯  東得克薩斯人  回到原點
That's right, East Texas. Close the circle.
我去
I got it.
該我了
My turn.
肯定該我了
Definitely my turn.
一定要回來  斯圖
You come back, now, Stu.
要回來  弗蘭妮
You come back, Frannie.
月亮
M-o-o-n.
-還有那個咒語  -我們會回來的
- And that... that spell... - We'll come back.
-保證嗎  -我保證
- Promise? - Promise.
小喬
Hey, Joe.
過來  小子
Come here, buddy.
需要你幫我照顧露西媽媽  好嗎
Need you take care of Lucy-mom for me, all right?
-嗯  -照顧好你所有的媽媽
- Yeah. - Take care of all your moms?
我會的
I will.
要聽話  來個擁抱
Be a good boy. Give me a hug.
你現在是頂梁柱了
All right, you're the man now.
好了
Okay.
再見  小喬  拜拜
See you, Joe-man. Bye.
-聽話哦  -我會的
- Mwah. You be good. - Okay.
史蒂夫
Steve.
主啊  主啊
Lords, yes. Lords, yes.
好了  記住  走支路  或者小路
Okay, now, remember, secondary roads, or even tertiary.
除非你們想每十五分鐘
Unless you want to be winching cars out of your way
-就拖車清路  -我是在鄉間公路上長大的
- every 15 minutes. - Hey, I grew up backroading
而弗蘭妮大概有幾千張地圖  這寶貝馬力很足
and Frannie's got just about a thousand road maps and this baby's a tank.
沒錯  我們會沒事的
She is. We'll be just fine.
-我們會沒事的  -對  她就像臺小坦克
- We'll be all right. - Yeah. She-she's just a tank.
湯姆
Tom.
-我會想你的  -好的
- I'll miss you. - All right.
我也會想你的  伙計
I'll miss you, too, pal.
-愛你  兄弟  -我愛你
- Love you, buddy. - I love you.
保重
Be good.
這是我聽過最瘋狂的事了
It's the craziest thing I've ever heard.
-你們可能會死  -兄弟
- You guys could die. - Hey, man,
我們都還在這  還活著
all of us still here, still alive,
經歷了超級流感和弗拉格
after the super flu and after Flagg--
那才是真正的奇跡
I mean, that's the real long shot.
這個只是小菜一碟
It's a piece of cake.
愛大家
Love you guys.
-我們愛你們  -愛你們
- We love you. - Love you.
愛你們
Love you.
那我們出發了
All right, we're off.
回頭見
See you guys!
-拜  -拜
- Bye! - Bye!
-我們不在的時候別玩的太瘋了  -愛你們
- Don't have too much fun without us. - Love you!
-再見了  -拜
- Bye, you guys. - Bye!
好了  拉吧
All right, take it up!
可以了告訴我
Say when.
好了
Yep, there you go.
有用嗎
Is it working?
有
Yep.
好  拉
All right. Pull.
再來點  再來點
All right, little more, little more.
停
All right, hold.
我們今晚吃什么
What do we got tonight?
我們吃...廚子說了算
We got... dealer's choice.
謝謝  親愛的
Thanks, honey.
歡迎來到內布拉斯加州
植樹節之家
內布拉斯加州  洛頓
不如我們在這里過夜吧
What do you say we, um, stop there for the night?
-有人需要換衣物  -沒問題
- Someone needs a change. - Yep. Sounds like a plan.
今天開了四百英里  能信嗎
Made 400 miles today. Believe that?
我的背能信
My back believes it.
如果繼續如此
Keep on like this,
我們這周末就能看到大西洋了
we'll be looking at that Atlantic Ocean by the end of the week.
坐在你父母家的門廊上  喝著檸檬汁
Sitting on your folks' porch and sipping lemonade.
我想我們能在這待一晚
I think I can settle for this tonight.
你能先進去看看嗎  我和孩子待在車上
Would you mind if the kiddo and I stayed out here while you...
沒問題
You got it.
我了解
I know the drill.
好男人
Good man.
好了  小家伙
All right, little one.
你該出來了
Time to get you out.
來吧  小子
Come on, boy.
這地方沒人
Place is clean.
柜子里有些罐頭食品
Bunch of canned goods in the pantry,
但都脹氣了  不能吃了
but they're all swole up. It's no good.
上個鎮我們開車經過了一個超市
There was a supermarket that we passed in the last town.
看起來沒被洗劫
Didn't look looted.
對  但都過去十英里了
Yeah, that's ten miles back, though.
我們有很多食物  對吧
We got plenty of supplies, don't we?
對  但我們得留著
Yeah, well, we got to conserve them.
如果可以的話再添加  之前還有個藥店
Add to them, if we can. And there was a drugstore.
我們可以給這個小家伙買點磨牙的藥
We can get some Numzit for this little one.
對  但她現在睡著了  對吧
Yeah, yeah, but she's sleeping now, isn't she?
也不會睡太久
That won't last.
你聽到了嗎
You hear that?
什么
What's that?
寧靜
The quiet.
嗯
Yeah.
看那個月亮
Look at that moon.
你想要月亮嗎  弗蘭妮
You want that moon, Frannie?
我會扔套索幫你摘月
I'll throw a lasso around that moon for you.
這個說法怎么來的
What's that from?
*水牛城姑娘  今晚出來好嗎*
*Buffalo girls, won't you come out tonight*
我無懼惡魔
I will fear no evil.
-我帶她進屋  外面太冷了  -好
- I'm gonna take her inside. It's getting awfully cold. - Yeah.
科杰克  我們走
Kojak, let's go!
*耶穌*
*Oh, Jesus*
*過來好嗎*
*Won't you come by yere*
*耶穌*
*Oh, Jesus*
*過來好嗎*
*Won't you come by yere*
*現在是需要您的時候了*
*Now is the needed time*
*現在*
*Oh, now*
*是需要您的時候了*
*Is the needed time*
*現在是需要您的時候了*
*Now is the needed time.*
寶寶在長牙呢
Baby teething.
你確定你們倆不想來陪著我嗎
You sure you two don't want to come to keep me company?
我不想把她弄醒了
I don't want to wake her.
那牙讓她半宿都睡不著
That tooth kept her up half the night.
好吧
Oh, right.
-那再拿點嬰兒用泰諾  -嗯  布洛芬也行
- So, more baby Tylenol - Yeah, or Motrin.
-布洛芬  -你能再拿點水嗎
- Motrin. - And can you get some water, too?
這邊的東西都不能用
There's nothing here that works.
遵命  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
給
Here.
我得要你...  看著點外面
I'm gonna need you... to keep an eye out.
好嗎
All right?
弗蘭妮·奧克利
Frannie Oakley.
-小心點  -好
- Be careful. - Yep.
*水牛城姑娘  今晚出來好嗎*
*Buffalo girls, won't you come out tonight*
*今晚出來好嗎*
*Won't you come out tonight...*
當心你的新牙  小英雄
Watch the new teeth, little hero.
*水牛城姑娘  今晚出來好嗎*
*Buffalo gals, won't you come out tonight*
*我們在月光下舞動起來*
*And we'll dance by the light of the moon.*
好了
All right.
東西挺全
The mother lode.
覺得那個舊水泵還能用嗎
Think that old pump still works?
想看看嗎
Want to find out?
*因為你的吻讓我飛上云霄*
*'Cause your kisses lift me higher*
*宛若天籟之聲讓我魂銷*
*Like the sweet song of a choir*
*你炙熱的愛*
*And you light my morning sky*
*如同我的晨曦*
*With burning love*
媽的
Shit.
真是太好了
Terrific.
我會小心的  別擔心
I'll be careful, don't worry.
*炙熱的愛*
*Oh, a hunk, a hunk o' burning love*
*A hunk, a hunk o' burning love.*
弗蘭  我遇到點小麻煩
Hey, Fran, I ran into a little trouble over here.
不是什么大事  就是輪胎扎了
Nothing serious, just a flat tire.
你聽到了嗎
You hear me?
弗蘭妮
Oh, Frannie?
弗蘭妮  你在嗎  收到回話
Frannie, you there? Come back.
你能聽見我說話嗎  弗蘭
Can you hear me? Fran?
我跟你說過要把對講機放身邊的  該死
I told you to keep the walkie next to you, goddamn it.
好吧  好吧
All right. All right.
來吧
Here we go.
水很干凈
It's good.
很冰涼
And cold.
你好  弗蘭
Hello, Fran.
你好  賤人
Hello, bitch.
撐住  寶貝兒
Hold, baby.
撐住
Hold.
弗蘭妮
Frannie.
就覺得你可能會過來
Thought you might drop by.
你死了啊
You're dead.
可我在這
Yet here I am.
我是在做夢
I'm dreaming this.
可能是你死了
Well, maybe you're dead.
有你的來世  還是算了吧
An afterlife with you in it. I don't think so.
我們先把這事放一邊吧  怎么樣
Well, let's table the issue for now, shall we?
我想給你看個東西
I want to show you something.
地球上從未因為與現代人發生接觸
One of the last tribes on Earth
而受到污染的僅存的部落之一
never polluted by contact with modern man.
曾幾何時
Once upon a time,
很多這樣的部落被傳教士滅了門
entire tribes like this were wiped out by missionaries
把沾了天花病毒的毯子送給了他們
who gave them blankets with smallpox.
這些土著們...
These fine folks...
都沒被超級流感侵襲過
they weren't even touched by the superflu.
這多諷刺啊  你不覺得嗎
It's ironic, don't you think?
總之吧...  談正事
Anyway... to business.
你沒死  寶貝兒
You're not dead, honeybunch.
但就快了
But you will be soon.
我不清楚你的頭骨是否摔裂了
I don't know if your skull is fractured,
還是僅僅是個腦震蕩
or if it's only a concussion.
我不是醫生  但我在電視節目上扮演過
I'm not a doctor, but I play one on TV.
我能確定的是你的右腿
I do know that you suffered multiple fractures
多處骨折
on your right leg.
你的膝蓋骨碎了  髖關節骨折
Your knee is blown out, your hip shattered.
三根肋骨骨折
Three broken ribs.
你看見從嘴里流出的血了嗎
And do you see that blood coming out of your mouth?
其中一根肋骨刺破了的肺  很糟糕
One of those ribs has punctured your lung. Nasty.
我才不信你呢  你總是騙人
I don't believe you. You lie.
對  這是我眾多本領之一
Yes. One of my many talents.
這事我沒撒謊  你也很清楚
I'm not lying about this and you know it.
艾比蓋爾寶寶餓了
Baby Abagail's getting hungry.
多么無助  多么脆弱
So helpless. So fragile.
現在  你的鄉巴佬騎士
Now, will your redneck knight
能及時趕回去救她嗎
make it back in time to save her?
我們來看看
Let's see.
那車看起來不太穩定  你覺得呢
That truck looks mighty unsteady, don't you think?
這我也不信
I don't believe that either.
但我現在很寬容
But I'm in a forgiving mood.
很治愈
A healing mood.
斯圖換輪胎的時候或許不會被壓扁
Stu might change that tire without getting squashed.
你可能最多就是
And you might have suffered nothing worse than
腦袋上腫個小包
a little bump on the noggin.
你覺得怎么樣
Would you like that?
沒有代價嗎
Free?
當然沒有代價
Well, of course it's free.
你把我當成什么庸人了
What kind of a philistine do you take me for?
只有一件小事
There's just one little thing.
我想吻你
I would like a kiss.
我可能還會想偶爾通過你的眼睛
And I might want to take a little peek
偷偷看一下
through your eyes from time to time,
看看外面怎么樣
just to see how things are going.
你想占有我的軀體
You want to possess me?
是嗎  就像你對哈羅德和納丁那樣
Is that it? Like you did Harold and Nadine?
我的老朋友弗洛伊德醫生肯定會稱之為
That is what my old friend Dr. Freud would call
"過度夸張"
"An hysterical exaggeration."
不不不
No, no, no, no.
你真的想死在那個井里嗎
Do you really want to die in that well?
難道你不愿意
Wouldn't you rather live
和你英俊的丈夫一起撫養寶貝女兒嗎
with your handsome hubby and raise your bouncing baby girl?
我當然想
Of course I want that.
那就吻我
Then kiss me.
除非你是上帝本尊
Not if you were God Himself.
我一點都不信  這都是謊言
I don't believe any of this. This is all a lie.
也許是吧
Perhaps it is.
但你知道  你的寶貝女兒現在正躺在門廊上
But you know that your little baby is out on that porch...
而且只有她一個人
and she is all alone.
她在哭
She is crying.
她很餓
She's hungry.
她想要媽媽  但她的媽媽馬上就要死了
She wants her mama, but her mama is dying!
一個吻  你就能活下來
One kiss... and you will live
看著她成長為堅強善良的女人
to see her grow up to be a strong and kind woman.
剩下的我們之后再談
We'll discuss the rest later.
為了我的丈夫
Not for my husband!
為了我的孩子和這個世界  我絕不會這么做
Not for my baby! Not for the world itself!
滾到我身后去吧  你這混蛋
Get thee behind me, you fucking bastard!
*耶穌  過來好嗎*
*Jesus, won't you come by here*
*現在是需要您的時候了*
*For now is the needed time*
*Now is the needed time*
*現在是需要您的時候了*
弗蘭妮
Frannie?
-教母  -弗蘭妮·古德史密斯
- Mother? - Frannie Goldsmith,
你在這里干什么
what are you doing here?
我不在這里
I'm not here.
我不在這里  我在井里
I'm not here. I'm in a well.
我覺得我快死了  還有我的
And I think I'm dying and my...
-孩子  -弗蘭妮
- my baby... - Frannie.
他只是讓你看到了他以為會讓你害怕的東西
He simply showed you what he thought would scare you
來讓你按他的意愿行事
into doing his will.
他是其父之子
He's his father's son,
而且他誘惑了你
and he tempted you.
但你拒絕了誘惑
But you resisted that temptation,
上帝會保佑你
and God will bless you.
來吧  過來
Come on. Come here.
過來吧  孩子  過來
Come on here, girl. Come here.
我可以死
I can die.
我可以死  但別讓我的孩子死
I can die, but not my baby.
不  弗蘭妮  不會讓你的孩子死
No, Frannie, not your baby.
弗蘭妮  親愛的  快回答我
Frannie, baby, come on, pick up.
該死
Aw, damn it.
你怎么跑到路上來了
What you doing out here in the road, boy?
走吧
Go on!
一切看起來都很好
You know, all seems well...
然后上帝來了  祂說  "不
and then here comes God and says, "No,
"還有更多事要做
"There's more to do,
還有更多痛苦要承受"
more pain to bear."
上帝很殘忍
God is cruel, then.
約伯也這么說
Job said the same.
然后上帝從旋風中向他傳話  祂說
And God spoke to him out of the whirlwind, and He said,
"當我創造世界的時候  你在這里嗎"
"Were you here when I made the world?"
上帝說"時過境遷
God said, "The wheel keeps turning,
斗爭延續
The struggle continues,
但是命令
But the command...
始終如一
Is always the same.
保持本真
Be true.
堅持"
Stand."
弗蘭妮
Frannie?
弗蘭
Fran?
上帝啊
Oh, Jesus.
弗蘭妮
Frannie!
弗蘭
Fran!
弗蘭妮
Frannie!
我能夠知曉事物  弗蘭妮·古德史密斯
I'm in the way of knowing things, Frannie Goldsmith.
我知道你將會有五個孩子
I know that you'll be the mother of five.
這五個孩子又會生下20個孩子
These five will bring forth 20
這20個孩子又會生下70個孩子
and the 20 will bring forth 70,
你還能親眼看到這70人中的幾位呢
and some of those 70 you will live to see.
看啊
Behold,
你的孩子將會讓地球重新煥發生機
your children will replenish the Earth.
堅持住
H-Hang tight, all right?
我來救你出來
I'm gonna get you out of there.
我可以把繩子放下去  但是她沒辦法
I can get the line down to her, but she's not gonna be able
-抓住繩子  -我來拉繩子
- to hang on. - I'll pay out the cable.
你下去把她救上來
You ride it down and bring her up.
什么  什么
What? What?
狗  去看寶寶
Dog. Baby.
好  放繩子
All right, let it out.
堅持住  寶貝
Hang on, baby.
希望你知道你在做什么
Hope you know what you're doing.
我知道  把她救上來就行了
I do. You just get her.
好了  放放放
All right, go. Go, go, go.
再放一點
More!
好了
All right, whoa!
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
我知道很疼
I know it hurts.
收繩
Pay out!
我來救你了  我來救你了  親愛的
I got you, I got you, honey.
準備好了嗎  數到三
All right, ready? On three.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
好了  把我們拉上去
Okay, pull us up!
來  寶貝
Come on, baby.
慢點  慢點
Easy, easy.
-她都快沒氣了  -給我一點空間  斯圖爾特
- She's barely breathing. - Give me some space, Stuart.
什么
What?
你怎么知道我名字的
How do you know my name?
天啊
Oh, my God.
看起來還不錯
Looks good.
坐起來  弗蘭妮
Sit up, Frannie.
我應該不行
I don't think I can.
來吧
Come on.
現在  站起來
Now stand.
你沒事吧
You okay?
真的沒事嗎
Like, really okay?
都不疼了
Nothing hurts.
都不疼了  斯圖
Nothing hurts, Stu.
艾比
Abby.
我知道  我也嚇壞了
I know. I was scared, too.
是的  小家伙
Yes, cute thing.
緬因州  奧甘奎特
一周后
你從來沒見過大西洋吧  東得克薩斯人
Never seen the Atlantic, have you, East Texas?
我在照片和電影里看到過  但不是像這樣
I mean, I've seen it in pictures and movies, but not like this.
這...這真是完全不一樣
That's... That is something else, isn't it?
你現在知道我為什么很想來了吧
Now you understand why I wanted to come?
是的
Yes, I do.
你也喜歡這風景吧
You like the look of that, don't you?
告訴我  斯圖
Hey, tell me something, Stu.
你覺得再生四個
How would you feel about having
這樣的小家伙這么樣
four more of these little rascals?
我原本想再生兩個就差不多了
Well, I was thinking more like two.
再說吧
We'll see.
我是一個很容易被說服的人
I'm easily persuaded.
在內布拉斯加州的時候
Hey, uh, back in Nebraska...
發...發生了什么
what... what happened?
我在那里...
What happened is that I...
發現了這個世界有兩面
I found out that there are two sides to the world.
這一面
There's this...
還有一口...
...and then there's...
黑暗的深井
...a deep well of darkness.
一個坑
A pit.
我在那個深井里瀕死的時候  我同時看到了
And when I was dying in that well, I saw both of them.
我受到了誘惑
And I was tempted.
"時過境遷
"The wheel turns..."
斗爭延續
"...the struggle continues..."
而命令始終如一"
"...and the command is always the same."
什么命令
And what command is that?
保持本真
Be true.
堅持
Stand.
你們好嗎
How's it hanging?
拜托
Come on.
*我們為什么不能做朋友*
*Why can't we be friends*
我叫拉塞爾·法拉第
My name is Russell Faraday.
崇拜我
Worship me!